Friends, if you have Fast Tag and
you have sold your vehicle.  It can be any
reason and if you have money lying inside it
then how can you get your money refunded
and how can you close this Fast Tag
from your mobile phone.
I am going to give you all the information step by step.
So watch this video from beginning to
end.  So guys, first of all
you have to open Chrome browser in your mobile phone.
After opening, what do you have to write in the search bar first
?  You have to write in the search bar
whatever company's past tag you have, like
I have ICICI company tag here,
you have to search it here.  Like
I have ICICI,
so when I searched here,
ICICI Bankst automatically came up, so you have to search this.
So as you search,
first of all you will get the link of this website here, that is,
you will reach the website of ICICI Bank.
So
I will click here and as you have past
tags and you are their customer, then you
just have to click on this
option here, after that a window will open in front of you.
After that, here you have to
click on individual login
because friends,
you are a fast hack customer of ICICI Bank.  You have to
click here.  After that here you
get two options one and two.  If you have a
login ID, then
log in with your login ID.  If you
don't have a login ID, you need the mobile number
that is linked to your West Tag.  Then
you have to log in your mobile number here and
click here.  After clicking,
your number will be asked here
and you have to enter this captcha here.
As soon as you enter,
you have to click on this request for OTP here.  Then you will receive
OTP.  You have to enter the OTP that will come here
and you have to check mark this box.
After that you have to click on login.
So we fill up this information quickly.
So friends,
we have entered all these information.  Here enter the mobile
number, verification code and OTP and
check mark this box.  After that,
you will see that you have to click on login below.
So friends, as soon as you click on login,
you will get this kind of notification here.  You have to do it no.
Here your KYC etc. will be asked.
So as soon as you click, first of all
you will be shown here how much current balance you have
in the Fast Tag.
As it is written here 420 sorry 425,
my current balance here is ₹425.
So here I will refund it to my bank
because this fast tag is of
no use to me.  I have
sold my vehicle.  So now
I want to get this money in my account.
For that, friends, you
will see here that you will get the option of close account.
Here you have to click
on Close Account because you will get your refund only when your account is closed.
So
I'm going to click here.  After that,
you will get some key points here in which
you will be told about the cost tag.   That means,
you will be shown information about when your payment will arrive.
You can read this.
After reading, you have to click on I Agree.
After clicking, you have to
click on Accept here.  As soon as you click here,
your close account
information will appear here.  First of all you have to check
mark it.  After checking the check mark, the
reason will ask you
why you want to close your account
?  So here you can write
in very soft English that I have sold my car.
So friends, here
I have written that I have sold the car.   That means
I have sold my car.
After that you have to slide up again.
After sliding up,
you have to enter the details of some documents here.
Like name of the person, your name, in whose
name the vehicle was or in whose name this tag was,
after that the ID proof can be your Aadhar card.  It could be
PAN card sorry voter card.
So, whatever information is asked here,
I am filling it out for you
so that you do not make any mistake.  So
friends, finally I have filled this form.
What did you do first?  First of all,
I entered my name here because there is a
fast tag in my name.  After that,
Aadhar card was asked for as ID proof.  There
are many IDs here like PAN card, Voter ID etc.
You can select as per your requirement.  I
selected Aadhar Card here.
I have uploaded
my Aadhar card here as ID proof.  Apart from this, if you have any other
document then you can attach it here.
Otherwise you can leave it blank.   It
is optional.  After that passbook or cheque.
If you have a passbook, you can put its photo here
or you can also put a cancellation cheque.
After that, bank details have been
asked from you here.  Name of the bank,
where is the branch?  What is your account number?
You have to enter the account number twice for confirmation.
After that, account holder name i.e. in
whose name is this account?  What is IC code
?  Its account type is savings or
current account.  You have to fill this here,
which I have done and shown you here.
All this information is
written in your passbook.
Where is the branch name? What is the branch name?  What is the name of the bank
?
You can see your profile in the front page of your passbook.
After doing this,
Close Account appears here.  You have to click here.
So you can see that it is written here that
Tag Account Close Request has been sent
for approval.  That means my
application has been sent.  And
now I will have to wait for the approval here.
And friends, it has already been
written to you in the remarks here.  You can also see.
Close account request sent
for approval.  That means that requirement for approval has been
sent, that is, it has gone
and here it will appear like this.
If there is any error, it will
ask you to enter your details again.
So this type of show will happen with you also
as you are seeing in this video
and now you can log out of this account
and also log in and see whether
your account has been closed or
not.  As soon as your account is closed,
whatever your payment is,
mine is showing ₹425 here.  Whatever
your amount is, 100, 50, 2000, 2000, the amount will be
refunded to your bank account.
So friends, this was the process of
KISTAG, how will you get your money refunded in your bank account.
I have
given you all the information step by step.  I hope
you like the video and please like and
share it.  If you are new to the channel then please
subscribe to the channel so that
you can get a notification as soon as we upload a video.
Thanks for watching.